<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>plot on Welcome to Open Weed Science</title>
    <link>/tags/plot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in plot on Welcome to Open Weed Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/plot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One-way ANOVA for percentage weed control data</title>
      <link>/post/2019/12/20/one-way-anova-for-percentage-weed-control-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/12/20/one-way-anova-for-percentage-weed-control-data/</guid>
      <description>Background Assessments of visual weed control in response to herbicide treatments is likely the most common experiment and data analysis conducted within the Weed Science discipline. The goal of these experiments is to investigate herbicides that promote the best level of control of targeted weed species. These experiments are usually organized in a one-way randomized complete block design with multiple treatments (herbicides). At a pre-established number of days after treatment (DAT; researcher choice), a percent (%) visual control rate is given to each targeted weed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crop-weed competition in additive design</title>
      <link>/post/2019/12/13/crop-weed-competition-in-additive-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/12/13/crop-weed-competition-in-additive-design/</guid>
      <description>Background Crop–weed competition is extensively studied in weed science. The additive design, in which weed density varies and the crop density is kept constant, is the most commonly utilized design in plant competition studies. The additive design is important to calculate economic weed thresholds and improve weed control decision-making.
 Getting started  Download R for your laptop system/desktop from: https://www.r-project.org  R is a programming language and free software environment for statistical computing and graphics supported by the R Foundation for Statistical Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
